globaljournals.org 2010-12-11

# Privacy Policy | guideline | global-journals-research-portal

**Principles Governing This Site**

globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development is owned and published by the us,(“globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development”). Our publishing offices are located at Indore, India.

We take privacy issues seriously and are committed to protecting your personal information. Please take a moment to review our privacy policy, which explains how we collect, use, and safeguard information you enter at globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development. This privacy policy applies only to information collected by globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development through the globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development website. This privacy policy does not govern personal information furnished to globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development through any means other than the globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development website.

  * What Information Do We Collect?
  * How Is This Information Used?
  * What Security Measures Are Used?
  * How to Make Changes to Your Information
  * Other Information

What Information Do We Collect ?

Information You Provide to Us

We will request information from you if you establish a personal profile on our site to gain access to certain content or services, if you ask to be notified by e-mail about online content, or if you participate in surveys we conduct. This requires the input of personal information and preferences that may include, but is not limited to, details such as your name, address (postal and e-mail), telephone number, or demographic information. If you request paid content, including subscriptions, we will also ask for payment information such as credit card type and number.  
Information That Is Automatically Collected

 _Log Files  
_  
We use log files to collect general data about the movement of visitors through our site. This may include some or all of the following information: the Internet Protocol Address (IP Address) of the machine which accessed our website, host name, domain name, browser version and platform, date and time of requests, and the files downloaded or viewed. We use this information to measure and analyze traffic and usage of the 

globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development website.  
Cookies

We also use cookies to collect information and help personalize your online experience. Cookies are small files stored on your computer that we use to recognize you and your access privileges and preferences. Cookies allow you to store your username and password so you don’t have to log in each time you visit. We store minimal personally identifying information in cookies and protect this information. We do not store complete records or credit card numbers in cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies. Most browsers can be configured to prevent this, but you may not be able to access some parts of our site without cookies.

 _Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)_

We may also use clear gifs which are tiny graphics with unique identifiers that function similarly to cookies to help us to track site activity. We do not use these to collect personally identifying information.

## 

Information that you provide to us will be used to process, fulfill, and deliver your requests for content and services. We may send you information about our products and services, unless you have indicated you do not wish to receive further information.

Information that is automatically collected is used to monitor usage patterns at globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development in order to help us improve the site and its service offerings.  
  
**We do not sell or rent your e-mail address to any third party. You may unsubscribe from our e-mail services at any time. For additional information on how to unsubscribe from our e-mail services, please refer to the How to Make Changes to Your Information section of this Privacy Policy.**

We may report aggregate information about globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development usage to third parties, including our service vendors and advertisers. We may also disclose personal and demographic information about your use of globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development to companies and individuals we engage to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our Web servers, analyzing data, and providing marketing assistance. These companies and individuals are obligated to maintain your personal information as confidential and may have access to your personal information only as necessary to perform their requested function on our behalf.

### _Advertisers_

We may contract with third-party advertisers and their agents to post banner and other advertisements on our site, which may link to other websites not under our control. These third-party advertisers may use cookie technology or similar means to measure the effectiveness of their ads or may otherwise collect personally identifying information from you when you leave our site. We are not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials offered from such advertisers and their agents. Transactions that occur between you and the third-party advertisers are strictly between you and the third party and are not our responsibility. You should review the privacy policy of any third-party advertiser and its agent, as their policies may differ from ours.

## 

When you submit personal information via the globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development website, your information is protected both online and off-line with what we believe to be appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We will use the latest Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, which will encrypts your credit card and personal information.

## 

Once you have created an identity or paid account on our site, you can update your personal information at any time. You may also choose to stop receiving offer information from us about content or services. You can do this in several ways:

  * Send an e-mail message to  Admin@ComputerResearch.org  Admin@ComputerResearch.org  Admin@ComputerResearch.org  Admin@ComputerResearch.org  Admin@ComputerResearch.org  Admin@ComputerResearch.org  Admin@ComputerResearch.org  . Please include your e-mail address in the body of your message.
  * Contact our Customer Services Department at Indore, India or Customer Services, globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development.

## 

### Compliance with Legal Process

We may disclose personally identifying information if we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or legal process; (2) protect our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or the unauthorized use of our website; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public.

### Children

globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development is not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect or store any personal information from children under 13.

### Changes to This Policy

This privacy policy may be periodically updated. We will post a notice that this policy has been amended by revising the “Last updated” date at the top of this page. Use of globaljournals.org, GJ, Global Journals and Global Academy of Research and Development constitutes consent to any policy then in effect.
